How to talk about daily routines.
My daily routine is nothing special.
I usually wake up early, around 7
AM.
Breakfast is not important to me, so I
usually only drink a cup of coffee.
Sometimes, though, I will have an apple.
Breakfast is followed by a shower.
After I get dressed, I go to work.
Work is always the same during the morning.
I respond to emails and set up
meetings.
Around lunchtime, I start to feel really
hungry.
Often, my friends and I meet at a café
to have lunch together.
When dinner time comes around, however, I
cook dinner at home.
After dinner, I take my dog for a walk to
the park.
We can usually see the sunset, which is quite
beautiful.
I watch TV series or movies at
night.
There is nothing like a good movie before bed.
I sleep at 10 PM and then start the whole
routine over again the next day.